http://www.healthyskepticism.org/global/about/us/privacy

Healthy Skepticism
Join us to help reduce harm from misleading health information.
Advanced search
›
Home
What's New?
Privacy Policy
Healthy Skepticism takes the issue of personal privacy very seriously.
Any personal information which Members, Subscribers, Registered Guests or visitors to our website may have passed on to us is treated in the strictest confidence. We do not pass on personal data to any other organisation without the clear written consent of the individual involved.
We are not involved in the sale of personal information and have been actively involved in campaigning against such practices.
We are keen to work with industry insiders and former industry staff. We keep the identity of these people strictly confidential for their protection.
Communications or queries contained in emails or via other means of communication from people may be discussed within our organisation with a view to providing the best response to the communication, but the contents of the communication will not be divulged to third parties without the person’s explicit consent.
Our website uses cookies strictly for internal management purposes.
If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy please contact:
.(JavaScript must be enabled to view this email address)
Comments
Our members can see and make comments on this page.
Please
Register
(read more) then
Log in
for free access to more features of this website.
Forgot your username or password?
You are invited to
apply for membershipof Healthy Skepticism, if you support our aims.
Pay a subscription
Support our work with a donation
Buy Healthy Skepticism T Shirts
If there is something you don't like, please tell us. If you like our work, please tell others.
Announcements
PharmedOut’s annual conference: Missing The Target: When Practitioners Harm More Than Heal
No Free Lunch is merging with Healthy Skepticism
Conference program: Pharma Knows Best? Managing Medical Knowledge
Prescrire’s proposals for France’s national conference on medicines policy
Pharmed Out Conference ‘Pharma Knows Best? Managing Medical Knowledge’
More announcements
What's new on this site
About HS
As an advertising man, I can assure you that advertising which does not work does not continue to run. If experience did not show beyond doubt that the great majority of doctors are splendidly responsive to current [prescription drug] advertising, new techniques would be devised in short order. And if, indeed, candor, accuracy, scientific completeness, and a permanent ban on cartoons came to be essential for the successful promotion of [prescription] drugs, advertising would have no choice but to comply.
- Pierre R. Garai (advertising executive) 1963
Our main aim is improving health by reducing harm from misleading health information.
We are an international non-profit membership association incorporated in South Australia: A8764, ABN 43 390 138 359.
Everyone who supports our aims is welcome to join us.
